v! What are you readng?
Romeo and Julet.
Shakespeare, eh?
What's wth the sarcastc tone?
You're just actng lke that
because you've never read t.
lf you really read t, you'd know
Shakespeare s vulgar and tasteless.
You thnk so? l enjoy hs works.
lt's a masterpece full of chaos and energy,
yet t's also acute, reflectng socety at that tme.
Though they knew t wasforbdden,
Romeo and Juletfell n love.
Thefeud between the twofamles
could be compared to thefeud...
...over the Brtsh throne between
the Houses of York and Lancaster.
You're brllant, Prnce Hakm! So nsghtful!
Though,forbdden love exsts n every era.
Rven now, n late 1 9th century ctoran Rngland.
l'm sorry! Are you all rght!?
l ddn't realze anyone was there!
William is a member of the
upper class, called the gentry.
l ddn't realze anyone was there!
William is a member of the
upper class, called the gentry.
Emma is a humble maid.
Such bad tmng! That's just lke you.
Yet Williamfell in love with Emma at first sight.
l told you, ddn't l Rmma?
Since Kelly Stownar, Emma's mistress,
used to be William's governess...
l told you, ddn't l Rmma?
Since Kelly Stownar, Emma's mistress,
used to be William's governess...
That l used to be a governess.
Since Kelly Stownar, Emma's mistress,
used to be William's governess...
...it created an opportunityfor
the two to spend time together.
Well, that's a bt embarassng.
...it created an opportunityfor
the two to spend time together.
Gentry refers to the landed upper class,
ranked just below the arstocracy.
A governess s afemale tutor.
Ths s ctoran Trva.
Lace...
l would love to have even
a sngle lace handkerchef...
A handkerchef? A handkerchef!
ery well, l'll buy you 1 00, maybe 200!
What?
No please, wat!
Lace... lt's been a dream of mnefor years.
Lace?
Thank you so much, Mr. Jones.
Not at all...
Emma also came to love William,
because of his personable ways.
Hold t rght there!
lt's true that Romeo and Julet
s romantc, but ths s dfferent.
l'll never accept brother Wll
beng together wth a mad!
So even a chld who gets wrapped up n books
knows the dfference between dreams and realty.
Who are you callng a chld?
Yet, that brother of ours...
Ths s why you're such a bore.
As you can see, hs sblngs
are aganst ther relatonshp.
One after another, ther love
wllface many obstacles.
Who are you talkng to?
lt would seem you've turned down
every nvtaton you've receved.
l'm sorry.
William'sfather, Richard Jones, is a strict man.
lt's unlikely that he'll ever give them his blessing.
We may not have a ttle, but do you know
why our merchantfamly receves nvtatons?
Because of our money?
That s one reason. But we mustn'tforget
character, ntellgence and manners.
Those are the qualtes valued by polte socety.
Your personalfeelngs are mportant, of course.
But you must marry someone
from the same country.
She's not aforegner,father.
Rngland s one naton, but there
are two countres wthn t.
ln other words, the arstocracy
and the commoners.
Although these two countres share
the same language, they are dvded.
Then came a marriage proposalfor William.
Wllam?
lt's been such a long tme, Mrs. Campbell!
lt has ndeed.
ls yourfather well?
Yes, l'm pleased to say he stll
has a lot to sayfor hmself.
Good evenng. My name s Rleanor Campbell...
My name s Wllam Jones. Delghted to meet you.
You're qute good.
l never would have thought
ths was your frst dance.
Really?
Yes.
One, two, three! One, two, three!
The Jonesfamily would get the title of
Viscount from the Campbells.
One, two, three! One, two, three!
The Jonesfamily would get the title of
Viscount from the Campbells.
One, two, three!
Just lke that. You're dong great!
The Campbells would get
the Jonesfamilyfortune.
Just lke that. You're dong great!
The Campbells would get
the Jonesfamilyfortune.
When you ht the ball, brng your wrst back.
lt was a welcome idea, since
their marriage would benefit bothfamilies.
When you ht the ball, brng your wrst back.
lt was a welcome idea, since
their marriage would benefit bothfamilies.
lt wll be wonderful f the match wth
the Jonesfamly goes through, won't t?
Don't make so much nose!
Who are you talkng about?
Mrs. Campbell's daughter.
What?
Ths sn't 50 years ago.
Just because the parents have
made up ther mnds about marrage,
t doesn't mean the chldren
must comply wth ther wshes.
William adamantly refused.
However, something uneXpected happened.
Eleanor, the lady in question,
hadfallen in love with William.
That's not true! l really enjoy talkng wth hm!
l wonder... f Wllam already
has someone that he lkes?
Oh dear! Just lsten to me babble...
Rleanor, you have to know. l...
l'll watfor you.
What...?
lt doesn't have to be today, or tomorrow.
l really don't mnd...
So please, nvte me out agan...
...because, l'm watngfor you.
But, William didn't want to hurt Eleanor, so...
...in the end, he never told her about Emma.
Furthermore, William's siblings were
vehemently against their relationship.
She's a mad.
A mad...?
Hey, you! l don't know what your ntentons are,
but you should just gve up and go home!
Brother Wll's stupdty s one thng,
but you don't have any common sense ether!
A servant s a servant. A master s a master.
How do you not understand somethng so smple-
v!
Sster, what are you dong? Let me go!
But perhaps the biggest obstaclefor William
was that several menfancied Emma.
l know that t's sudden,
and that we've only just met.
Forgve me, l don't mean to
cause you trouble... That s...
You see,
l love you.
l'm speechless at your shallow actons.
l can't beleve you'd do such a thng.
l thought you were better than that.
Why? Rmma s such an amazng woman.
l would have done anythng to make her mne.
"Make her mne?" Prnce Hakm,
don't say such vulgar thngs!
Although ther relatonshp had a number of
obstacles, some were wllng to help them.
Got you!
Touché. Pont.
To Mr. and Mrs. Knox!
Al, you're not as strong wth
alcohol as you used to be.
l've always been weak where
lades and fne wne are concerned!
Emma and William's biggest supporters...
...were Emma's mistress Kelly, and Al,
who was best friends with Kelly's late husband.
l've never met anyone lke hm.
Although he's of the gentry,
he doesn't seem to notce that l'm a mad...
lt's true... that young man
can be rather careless.
He doesn't ask me smple "yes or no"
questons lke others do...
...he always seems happy just to talk.
Do you lke hm?
l see...
Rmma!
Thank heavens. l thought l'd lost you.
Yes...
But, why dd you come to ths spot?
Because you sad that thefountan
was used as a meetng place.
l thought that you mght come back here...
Me too! l had afeelng that you'd be here!
Are you tred?
No... l saw so many thngs that l'd never
seen before, l thnk my eyes must be n shock.
Thus, the two confirmed
theirfeelingsfor each other.
Ther date was held at the Crystal Palace.
The botancal exhbt there,featurng plants
from around the world, s especally magnfcent.
Ths s because Joseph Paxton,
the archtect, was orgnally a gardener.
A gardener s a servant who tends to plants.
Ths s ctoran Trva.
However, a cruelfate awaited Emma.
Ma'am...?
Ma'am...
Your pocket watch has been fxed...
Ma'am!
All alone, Emma went to the Jones estate
for the first time, to see William.
lt's true, sn't t...
l kept thnkng that we lved n the same place.
You both lve n the same Rngland.
No, we don't.
Comng here, l understand.
l realze that the worlds we lve n...
are completely dfferent.
l ddn't know. l'm... so sorry...
lt must have been so lonely...
Mr. Jones...
You should be ashamed.
l've done nothng to be ashamed of.
lt's you who should be ashamed,father.
Could you leave us now?
l'll make certan you are well pad.
Father!
Rxcuse me.
Rmma!
Stop rght there!
How could you say such a thng?
Rmma!
Out of love, Emma chose to leave,
to protect William from getting hurt.
William made the same choice.
When she really needed someone
by her sde... l couldn't be therefor her.
Dd l... ever really know her?
l was only thnkng of myself. l ddn't
consder what would make Rmma happy.
Well... l wanted to consder herfeelngs.
But Rmma was sufferng so badly.
Rven f l decded to marry Rmma,
she would have to take on the Jones name.
She'd be bound by the strct tradtons of
polte socety, exposed to the curosty of others...
Sacrfcng so much, would Rmma
ever really be happy marryng me, l wonder?
You love Rmma...
...and Rmma loves you.
What else do you want?
Why are you so confused?
l don't understand you at all.
More mportantly, f you don't hurry and
stop Rmma, you'll never see her agan.
What do you mean?
Rmma!
Thank you so much.
Rmma...
Rmma!
Also out of love, William
couldn't stop her from leaving.
Emma parted ways with William,
and left Kings Cross Station to go
back to the village where she was born.
Because they truly loved one another,
they would no longer be together.
lt's a typcal endng to a tragc love story.
Romeo and Julet's death brought
the twofeudngfamles together, but...
...Wll and the mad's separaton
ddn't create anythng postve.
ln that sense, maybe l shouldfeel badfor hm.
l wouldn't be so sure.
Oh, t seems we've got the wrong number.
We stll have tme to change t,
so please hurry back to the tcket wndow.
Oh!
Lady Dorothea. This chance encounter with her...
l'm so sorry. l mstook youfor someone else.
...will bring Emma and William's
fates together once again.
l'm so sorry. l mstook youfor someone else.
...will bring Emma and William's
fates together once again.
lt's all rght.
...will bring Emma and William's
fates together once again.
That's beautful...
lt's a lly of the valley, sn't t?
Yes... though l'm not sure why l bought t.
Oh, don't worry about that!
Flowers are great to have anywhere.
ln the "language of flowers," that lly s
wonderful, too. Do you know what t means?
No...
lt means that "happness wll return."
The actors have taken ther place.
The second act s about to begn.